# James Adedamola

linkedin.com/in/james-adedamola-2678b8241

## **ReactJS Developer**

2 years of experience leading Frontend Development, including winning the Developer of the Month award in 2022 at SIMT Educational Consults. In 1 year, I successfully built projects from scratch to completion and drove innovation at CyberChipers as their CEO.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### CyberChipers

**CEO** 

· Leading Frontend Developer

SIMT Educational Consults • Lagos • Full-time • 01/2022 - 02/2023

### Frontend Developer

• I won the Developer of the month in 2022

Earnest-ly • Lagos ,Nigeria • Part-time • 01/2023 - 07/2023

A delivery and service provider company that aims in connecting workers to employers and also sell all kind of goods.

**ReactJS Developer** 

#### **EDUCATION**

## Degree in Computer Science

Lagos State University

## Associate of Science - AS in Computer Science

Adekunle Ajasin University

## Computer Science in Science

Lagos State University

#### CERTIFICATIONS

## Frontend Web Development

Udemy • 01/2021 - 01/2023

#### **ReactJs Course**

Udemy • 01/2022 - 07/2023

## Frontend Web Development

AltSchool Africa • 01/2022 - 01/2023

#### **AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS**

### Developer of the month

AltSchool Africa • 06/2022

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Simt Educational Consults

Simt Educational Consult • 11/2021 - 06/2022

I created a multipage website using ReactJS and the latest technologies, and led a team of skilled developers to make sure the interface was intuitive and user-friendly.

## Earnest-ly

Earnest-ly • 01/2023 - 07/2023

I spearheaded the development of their website together with my team of developers and skilled tech-related individuals to make sure we used our skills and experience to create the best possible user-experience.

#### **VOLUNTERERING & LEADERSHIP**

## CyberChipers

Co-founder • Lagos, Lagos • 06/2023 - 06/2024

Together with visionary and passion-driven people, we founded a company that is dedicated to giving you the best coding and cybersecurity teaching and experience possible. As their Frontend Developer and Co-founder, I work towards our success.

#### **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

Adobe Photoshop, Bootstrap, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Communication, CSS, Design, Engineering, English, Figma (Software), GitHub and Git, HTML5, Hugo, JavaScript, jQuery, Leadership, Less, Microsoft Excel, NodeJS, Problem Analysis, Problem Solving, Project Management, React.js, Strategy, Teaching, Team Leadership, Typescript, Al, Intuitive Design, Machine Learning, Web3